(Amy:)Should you really be
sitting in Sheldon's spot?
(Raj:)He's in Texas.
He'll never know.
(Penny:)I wouldn't be so sure about that.
(Leonard:)Yeah, he has a very sensitive butt.
(Leonard:)Well, it's true.
(Leonard:)Once I saw him sit on a bunch
of loose change and add it up.
(Raj:)Have you heard from Howard?
(Bernadette:)I did.
His talk at NASA went great.
(Penny:)Sheldon didn't heckle him?
(Bernadette:)No, in fact, he was so well-behaved,
(Bernadette:)Howie bought him a Buzz Aldrin
bobble head and astronaut ice cream.
(Stuart:)-Hey, guys.
-Hi, Stewart.
(Stuart:)-How's it going?
-Good .
(Raj:)Sheldon's out of town,
so we can do whatever we want.
(Raj:)We even ordered from
the Thai place he doesn't like.
(Stuart:)How is it?
(Penny:)Disgusting. Do not tell him.
(Leonard:)What do you guys want to do tonight?
(Amy:)I don't know.
(Bernadette:)I told Howie if I wasn't busy,
I'd spend the night at his mom's.
(Bernadette:)So for God's sake,
think of something.
(Raj:)Stuart? Are you okay?
(Stuart:)No, I don't feel so...
-Oh, Stuart?
-Stuart?
(Leonard:)Oh, my God,
you guys need to do something!
(Leonard:)Calling 911.
(Raj:)-It's too late.
-What do you mean it's too late?
(Raj:)He's been murdered
by someone in this room.
I (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(Leonard:)-Oh, my God.
-Come on!
(Raj:)Welcome to another classic
Koothrappali murder mystery dinner.
(Amy:)I'm leaving.
(Raj:)You can't leave.
(Raj:)You're a suspect in the
mysterious murder of Stuart Bloom.
I (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(Bernadette:)I didn't know his
last name was Bloom.
(Amy:)Yeah, it's Bloom.
(Penny:)Are you really gonna
lie on the floor
(Penny:)and pretend to be dead all night?
(Stuart:)What do you think
I was gonna do at home?